http://www.hamuniverse.com/privacypolicy.html

Tune
Around!SEARCHCQ-Calling All
Hams!About HamuniverseAntenna DesignAntenna Safety! Ask ElmerAbout BatteriesCode PracticeComputer HelpElectronicsFCC
InformationHam Hints  HumorHam Radio News!Post Reviews Product ReviewsHam Radio Videos! HF & ShortwaveLicense StudyLinksMidi MusicReading RoomRepeater Basics
Repeater
BuildersRFI Tips and
TricksHam SatellitesShortwave ListeningSSTVSupport The SiteSTOREVhf and UpContactSite MapPrivacy PolicyLegal StuffAdvertising Info
Hamuniverse.comPrivacy Policy (Updated
12-2013)
We collect no personal information about you when you visit
our website unless you choose to provide this information to us.
However, we or our host provider
collect and store certain information automatically using statistics
counters. Here is how we handle information about your visit to our
website. What We Collect and Store Automatically
If you do nothing during your visit but
browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will
gather and store certain information about your visit automatically.
This information does not identify you
personally.
We automatically collect and store only
the following information about your visit:
The
Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet
access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's
domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically
assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you
access our website; The type of browser, screen resolution and
operating system, and other technical information as needed for you to
gain access to our site such as; Your country, state, and city;
The date and time you access our site; Search terms used when
using search engines to find our site;The pages you visit; and if
you linked to our website from another website, the address (IP address)
of that website. We use the information we collect to count the number and
type of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make
our site more useful to visitors like you from a technical
standpoint.
Google Advertising on
Hamuniverse.com and your privacy!
We use third-party advertising
companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may
use information (not including your name, address,
email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and
other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and
services hopefullyy of interest to you. If you would like more
information about this practice and to know your choices about not
having this information used by these companies, click here.
personal information, as in e-mail with a comment or question. Most of our
email from visitors usually is from other licensed Amateur radio
operators. We DO NOT SELL, provide or in any way use your email address on
the website unless we have your express permission.All licensed
Amateur Radio Operator's "personal" information, (name, address, city,
state, callsign and license type, etc is easily avaliable on the Federal
Communications Commission website and other sites and is in the public domain. Most projects or
articles on Hamuniverse.com were submitted by licensed Amateur Radio
Operators for publication in the public domain
on this website along with their callsign and either/or their first and
last name and email address with their
permission via email contact or written or verbal authorization
from them to the webmaster, N4UJW, Don Butler of Hamuniverse.com.
We use the email address information provided from them or with
permisson from you to improve our service to you with the
projects so you may respond to them for your request for more
information about their projects or articles. Except for
authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share or sell their,
our (your) e-mail or email addresses with or to any other outside
organizations or individuals without your permission. We have no control
over your email address being copied by eye for any use. In other words,
if your email address is visible on a web page on this site, you gave
permission for it to be there and it can easily be copied by others for
whatever use they like. Your email address can be "hidden" from computer
generated "scavengers" by request from you. The
email address is only visible in a picture form or random text form rather
than in standard email format text. As an example of random text
format:n4ujw at hamuniverse dot com or,(insert your callsign or
email name here) at (your domain
name)Links to Other Sites
Our website has many links to other outside websites and
advertisers. In a few cases we link to private or pubic organizations.
When you click a link to another site (external from
Hamuniverse.com), or click on an advertisement, you are no longer on
our site and are subject to the privacy policy of that external site.
We have no
control over external links to other websites, thier content,
virus's or policies or the method they use to collect traffic
information.Disclaimer, Liability and Ownership Notice
Disclaimer Notice This website and the information it contains
is provided as a free public service to the Amateur Radio Community
primarily, and it's public visitors by N4UJW, Don Butler, Hamuniverse.com.
This system, (Hamuniverse.com),  is monitored internally and
externally to ensure proper operation, to verify the functioning of
applicable security features, and for comparable purposes. Anyone using this system expressly consents to such
monitoring. Unauthorized attempts to modify any information stored
on this system, to defeat or circumvent security features, or to utilize
the information on this system for other than its intended purposes are
prohibited and may result in criminal prosecution.
Restriction of Liability
Neither, Hamuniverse.com, N4UJW (Don
Butler) or others make any claims, promises or guarantees about the
accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and
expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of
this website. No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory,
including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third
party rights, title, copyright, merchantability, fitness for a particular
purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the
contents of this website or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources.
Reference in this website to any specific commercial products, processes,
or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the
information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute
endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by Hamuniverse.com unless
otherwise stated. Ownership of Site ContentsInformation
presented on this website, unless otherwise indicated by copyright ,
is considered in the public domain. It may be distributed or copied as is
permitted by the law. Not all information on this website has been created
or is owned by Don Butler, N4UJW or Hamuniverse.com. Most of the
information, especially in the projects and articles posted by others
contains a copyright by the owner (submitter) of the material and is
usually noted on each separate project or page with the proper credit to
the owner, author, etc. If you wish to use any
material from this website including graphics, text, drawing, diagrams,
pictures, html code or anything displayed on the viewable page or in the
html, on this or another website, you should always seek permission
directly from the owning (or holding) sources. Hamuniverse.com
shall have the unlimited right to use for any purpose, free of any change,
all information from articles and projects submitted to it except
those submissions made under separate legal contract. Hamuniverse.com
shall be free to use, for any purpose, any ideas, concepts, or techniques
contained in information provided to it for the betterment of the Amateur
Radio Community an the Ham Radio hobby.
Childrenâ€™s Personal Information
Consistent with the Childrenâ€™s
Online Privacy Protection Act:
This site does NOT collect, use, or disclose personal information (including online contact
information such as email addresses) of children under the age of 13.
In the event that we determine a child posts personal
information in a public forum such as a guest book or antenna forum, we
will delete that information once we become aware of it.
All emails, especially from children, sent to
Hamuniverse.com are confidential between us and them. We always tell the
children to get permission from their parents when contacting us in
future emails. Their email content will not be published or used in
any way unless permission if given by the legal parant or guardian.
The Antenna Formum is off site and we can not preview it
before it is made public but we do get a notice that new entries have
been made and deletion of personal information can be made at that time
by this webmaster. Due to heavy spammers on our guest book, it is no
longer in use!
Note: (Personal information would be defined as any information that could lead another person
directly or indirectly to a child or contact him or her directly
using that information.)
73!Don Butler N4UJW Webmaster
www.hamuniverse.com
&ampampltfont color=&ampampquot#006600&ampampquot&ampampgt&ampampampnbsp;&ampamplt/font&ampampgt
Hamuniverse.com uses Green
Geeks Web Hosting!
